

# Neeraj Vageele

Senior Software Engineer

## **My Contact**

meerajvageele451@gmail.com

+919924018566

Ahmedabad, India

www.neerajvageele.com

www.linkedin.com/in/neerajvageele-ba3801148/

#### **Technical Skill**

- Python Beginner
- JavaScript Experienced
- React JS-Experienced
- Node JS Experienced
- PostgreSQL Experienced
- AWS Services Experienced
- HTML/CSS- Experienced

## Languages

- English Fluent
- Hindi Fluent
- Gujarati Fluent

## **Education Background**

 Bachelor Of Engineering Computer Engineering Completed in 2017

#### **About Me**

Senior Software Engineer with 6 years of experience in software engineering. Self-directed leader with expertise in JavaScript based frameworks like ReactJS and NodeJS. Talented at cultivating collaborative and supportive team environment. Loves to solve real life problems using technology

#### **Professional Experience**

#### **Apexon | Senior Engineer**

2022 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- 1 year of experience in Health care software development.
- Led a team of 5-7 members, ensuring successful project delivery.
- Utilized Agile methodologies for efficient software development project management.
- Provided production support for the seamless functioning of software systems.

#### ThirdRock Techkno | Programmer Analyst

2017 - 2022

Key responsibilities:

- 5 years of experience in various domains, including E-commerce, E-learning, and Digital Transaction Management.
- Led a team of 8 members, ensuring successful project delivery.
- Created Projects from scratch using the MERN stack.
- Communicated effectively with clients, ensuring their needs were met and expectations were exceeded.

## **Latest Projects**

Jan 2023 – Present

#### MyAster (www.myaster.com)

- Worked with the front-end team
- Implemented landing page, checkout functionality, appointment booking, and teleconsultation feature, etc. in the project

May 2022 -Dec 2022

## Accelerate, HIMSS Solution (https://www.youraccelerate.com/)

- Client and on-shore team communication
- Team lead
- Implemented functionality in the Events module
- Research and integrated third party for an elearning solution